enjoy everyone this is Rahul Zaria from
sherka welcome back to exciting 3
actionable stop updates three basically
means right sector right quality and
right valuation these are our investment
ideas today we have an update on balam
Pini our analyst maintains B on balam
Pini with an unchanged price target of R
6150 isma has projected opening stock of
9.05 million tons as of oober 1st 2024
and sugar production of 33.3 million ton
without diversion this provides lot of
add room for the government to allow
ethanol production through sugar cane
juice and be heavy molases around 4 to
4.5 million T diversion might be allowed
further there is possibility of
government allowing around 2 million
tons of sugar export as Brazil is
expected to see lower production in the
current year domestic sugar prices are
expected to remain high with expected
lower inventory at end of second half
and likely increase in the sugar MSP
overall we expect sugar companies
including balamu Cheri to post good
recovery in the operating in fi25 and
expect stable performance in f26 stock
trades at 24 times fi25 and 20 * fi 26
estimated earnings next we have an
update on IC
Lombard our analyst maintains buy rating
on IC Lombard with a price target of
rupes 2550
the competitive environment has
relatively become favorable leading to
healthy underlying business Trends
providing Tailwinds to growth and
profitability we expect the company to
deliver Roe of 18 to 20% in near to
medium term at the current market price
the stock trades at 36.2 times at fi 26
and 30.3 times at SEI 27 earning EPS
estimates the stock has outperformed the
broader indexes in last 12 months
investment and securities Market are
subject to Market risks read all the
related documents carefully before
investing